The Be the
guy who
has back and back with
who
out pay
one begged.
Off. The force with two
lives come together
sometimes both good. Sometimes people.
And I am now and I'm definitely
a good. Time poster wanted to own this
is what it is dedicated to be ready in
about an hour now pick it up get your phone
centers around see if those papers are
on the way over to the executive as well.
Now Mr Darcy what's the score nice I'm
afraid it was effective the pressure went up
to share my regret I had
a gentleman I never in
a stock issues dividends or anything
else in your department I must run my
department with no interference either I
know why and when I need more factory
space or you need another boy and that's
alright with me too because I can take
these plants and pick my own spots and
motor production field you won't have to
worry so much about dividends that won't
be many but I have. I'm sure none of us
want to lose walk on our dividends want
to share with tech another vote in.
Favor of buying the three new
factor signify by Shanghai. I.
And you will not
a must vote Congratulations congratulate
the board of the winners. And these
backtrace themselves valuable and other
companies will jump at the chance to get
them on the no that you can buy them at
the price you want them how do I know I
bought them this morning I want
to come up all right that was
a Dell I was going to rush the stuff for
Mr Williams. Why don't you make it to kind
of the dentist I gave her the message by
this just. Thank you what about those
papers they're here for checking now.
Regulations Well take
a look at those provisions that means
that if I did. I want to leave
all right away just doing on the phone and
not mine. Directional. Myself and stick
with the Bill of Rights. But the
blueprints of that movie so I
don't want Jackson to sample. I'm afraid
now I won't be able to leave about
five o'clock was. Not going with me but
I counted on it and I thought as soon as
Dr Harris to kick out of whatever it was I
feel bad that I don't think. It would be
a very desirable driving companion.
Seriously you went along and
a little factories and. I'll send it back
to the office and cheat me out of my
goodbye kid not
a chance I get to drive over the
center of stuff on the way. But
I do.
Nothing in the whole world know this way
to do that just that we don't feel silly
grouches know damn well back way and give
me something to fix that close your eyes
relax. Take
a look at this if you
don't feel better. Oh.
Darling if you want to hold.
My bad not bad at all you know because my
life I like monograms on things it shows
they belong to me and close when they feel
like things I just say Mr Williams about
six years ago I married
a she gave me the first monogrammed shirts
I ever own those were the words on the
card I still haven't let me hope your
board of directors never discovered
a lot they want Don't worry. I have
only one dollar bills but. Really
happened this morning all I got out of
jealousy sucked out of the office and left
me a ride back and no time
a canary that is in your mouth. With those
bird's wings but short no one is going
to vote me down for you and I know I'm
right. But how did you convince the board of
that the politically was subtle and.
Then easy persuasion. Like that.
Either I get what I want or you get yourself
another boy and that's alright with me
to.
A place we don't be so
upset. I'll give you.
A little fun with this a little
take care that. I'm exactly
a good prescription for her you
know you're on. The way I feel now
a good catch them probably make
a new woman out of me not going to make
you too late. And I'm still at it by five
o'clock now while I'll run over to center
found that things are NOT be back for
a bike but I'm going away.
That's typically silly out take
a taxi cab to meet you in
Sausalito at the drugstore on
a corner off to the square I'll be there
at five o'clock when we get on the
straight out of town downstate all that
data traffic and all that time it'll take
to come and pick me up smart woman
my wife thinks of everything.
Like your back. And still has and things
are for. Sure you don't mind talking about
marriage. Sweeping. See at
five. Thirty get going. By the.
To.
The. Your.
Wall.
Hundred sixty seven nine seven to one.
Oh forget trying to stuff over the bell
boy at the airport hotel and open the
wallet for jackboot snack bar and the
apple hotel that's right at the check in
later. About but then I hear all the
stuff back to Oakland Yeah yeah
myself on the bike.
Where is that new woman that was going
to make me after five o'clock. Yeah
so sure you're going to be OK maybe you
better get this up another dentist. Court
there than any court just to prove it
to you I'm coming right on home no. You
really mustn't doubt or not I'm going to
be perfectly alright really and besides
what well I've done something and not find
a like you remember autobiography back in
Illinois I mean the old girl in Evanston
I'm aware you all might well it isn't money
this time it is another relative of her
favorite nephew Jim Tarrant. OK
Good to se when I get back well you don't
understand yet you're going to see him
right away what will always seem to want
us to be able to get back to Eleanor's So
I tell you I am
a tech and well it isn't that I offered
to kill but if he got huffy and said he
didn't want to handouts and well without
thanking I told him we'd take him up and
give him
a lift as far as Dan. I don't say I'm
good for you but where do I find this guy
when he should be there I know I
told him to be on the lookout for
a cream colored roadster just in case we
fail to recognize one another after all
these years. And yes such
a law usually forgive me but do you think
well I better run along because if you
might get nervous take it easy sweetie and
miss me when I do already don't drive
fast and police take. Off
and I Bella and that's when it wasn't able
to go with me now while I'm gone you see
that you get zero does every morning but
this time on all the cards with love from
self-pity Yeah S O F D Y.
Oh you must be Jim Tarrant Yeah that's me
I'm wild William I am all
right. But everything oh she's
a little under the weather the last
minute or so luck. It's too bad. So can I
say I'm disappointed to
wear your luggage. Less
trouble after.
Irene told me I had a
thrilling line. Going
a little rough. I'm exactly been
worried about my income tax. But your
line damn. Is in the better
salesman and they else.
Give you
a couple letters when you get back to Chicago
I might help you. Find the lane where
the top brass never heard. What I
disagree with. There and I mean.
I was
a. Rough step of the time and
actually I kinda like it that. This
outfit never got to. Go arse. Most
civilians never know or
care they need you to need
a. Little get that time. Or
last chance to check out for a while
but if you know that I grabbed
a hamburger when I was waiting
for you still say it's on.
You you want to send you money I'm
a gravel shot I. Can
say I was in the coke I want
chicken salad sandwich promise
anything for
a dollar. Thanks
.
Benefits go. Back to six seven one four.
One. Zero. With prices that
are one two five and I'm not
a. Baby apart Oh yes Mr William
No you made of net enough she said Mrs
Williams was taking something to make
a statement pleasant be
a step but perhaps no no don't
disturb her just that you have
a message that I won't forget
about that certain problem
I think I have if you watch
her can forget all about
a certain problem softy
that F O F T Y. Softy is
going to take out of their life that often
gets that's those who understand it but
be sure she gets it the
first thing the more.
Often if you as a loss I've been behind the
wheel of anything but I count a boomer
a Jeep I had a fine i want a real body
feels like why don't you drive through
a swamp nothing need better.
You know me or Irene still got that little
scar tissue. That once you got on the
floor yeah things are going to have now
that. You know about that you just got it
last summer that you said you hadn't seen
her for years. On the market of course.
How well you know it's just
getting those numbers.
Around are going to be pretty happy to
see you Irene that you're their favorite
nephew. But my lovely
cousin was just give me
a build up you. Get on
the Irene. Maybe not.
What's left of I think we got
a flat. Yeah
that is
a promise. Well if it worked here. I
got it quite
a drop. We're
going to. I think I have got
the jacket to go with. It.
If you find it. Yeah. I
don't want to be long.
Come on let's get going. We're.
Coming. Right out.
Of the.
Arena thinking.
Oh.
Damn.
You know.
There are recorders.
I.
Found my husband to be late had to rush
the planes be taking care. Of the Lispers
three
o two. The
.
Iranian the. Iranian name.
Now.
You're
you're.
.
They don't need. You they want to see
images walk away you understand I said but
she left orders not to be just dead they
were starting to get benefits and the
police department.
Thought.
Here and Lieutenant Quincy with the police
department I'm sorry to disturb you at
this hour with me I mean of course
well attendant did you know has been go on
a motor trip late this afternoon I went to
Denver on business why was he driving up
I could still yes is there anything wrong
I'm afraid that he needs to sit down
has. Something happened to my husband
yes Mrs Ugandans and
oh God I knew something like this would
happen I've begged him time and again not
to pick up hitchhikers I wanted wasn't
a hitchhiker Mrs Williams It was
just an accident he ran into
a truck gasoline truck
you mean there was fire
he must have been driving pretty fast I
don't think he felt anything after the
crash if
there's nothing more you need me father can
untie I think I understand but me I see
you've taken this with
a great deal of courage
Good night Mr Williams. I
agree.
A reading. Of what it was meant
but I got it how you want to
work for universal motors as
a sheet metal worker and Russian ten years
is their top production American leisure
without the blaze of glory their.
Ally.
The old
a are. Hiring
a stock. That.
A One of
a whole
a loser. One who. Could
use a dedicated place
a place to make. You
some telegrams from time to time just
put them under the door so little.
The all. The time when
I'm. Asking where.
You're. Going to. School.
When you feel pretty sure.
Our world.
You're on the road going the way he was
always then when he's away you seem to be
very fond of Mr Williams too many honor
to serve in five years. I'm sorry
to keep you waiting and I wouldn't be to
step in here again if it wasn't necessary
and I would be keeping it but I'm only
giving back on the town
everyone's been most thoughtful
and why shouldn't they be who
they give me I go right now what
a tenet the state police would like to
have some information they found some way
the skid marks were quite
a distance on the road as if the car had
been out of control when it crashed County
was Mr Williams a reckless driver
I know here he was a fast I have
a thirty knot record
when there was he was he
a heavy drinker quite the contrary but
what about his health could he have had
a heart attack and lost consciousness before
the accident I know he was in perfect
health but he didn't working much too
hard lately and and was over Tad
Perhaps he fell asleep at the wheel
last night oh heard shouting.
If only I didn't want to go with him are
starting right you'll be alive maybe you
should maybe you know it wasn't blame
yourself is it plays an important part in the
you.
When's the next plane to go and yet
to borrow. You sure there is more to
their lifestyle right.
Back out. I have.
I have
a car. Car is
a nephew important. Damn car I have.
Happened.
To all. Morning.
Long with. Or
knowing the warming and.
Cooling. Thing.
But that. Looks like
a duck that. They can't leave the station
but it was ducks and is just across the
road there Dr Think
you can make it yeah I'll make it.
Now take it easy man it's some concussion
that you've got to watch your step for
a while.
Walter Williams beautiful widow. By
her own request sat alone in the
family during the service.
Mark. Might have caught
her licking their chops.
The old.
It was. All the. Water What.
Is doing here is that they're getting the
dirty trick it can you name it oh wait
a minute don't touch it but
it turned out the police.
Homicide cop got on. The don't just came
into Washington the fingerprints are those
of a James Tague. Yeah I'm putting
Quincy on the right sort of opens up
a new canopies on the William is
actually that there's the F.B.I.
Report and a guy playing with
a lady's affection seems to come natural
rhythm all you got to do crazy to find
this which I got to do last known
whereabouts of Jim turns was in
a movie that somewhere between Jack and
Madden points based the wait a minute wait
a minute that's known address
care of the system as
a jersey for exactly everything about it
was Berkeley with what are you waiting for
Quincy that's good. Times live in
a holiday address so he said
he was going to. Travel to
all of the time and if you should happen
to hear from him would you like me don't
pay telephone bill in a bundle
of laundry laundry Let's have
a look
I may have to take this
along with not without
a receipt you don't you know you don't
trust the police in my business you don't
trust anybody My into.
Fully St Valentine's Day
Look you have the same
thing on here it's two.
Romance and you lit ten inch lights did
you ever see the lady you know I never
danced but I always know when she mean
you're wonderful person. I lay you tend to
one she's a rich widow
could be but I'll get you
a telephone that. Very fancy
stuff or even Yeah but he's
a pretty Eventually each I think
according to the shirt maker I said
a lady in the town had these made special
and they just like her husband only his
initials were W W shot or
smells don't it kept take
a look at this little item that was a
cellphone in the laundry. I the and W.
. When it could be when
you still couldn't.
Promise I can answer the L O L If it's.
What you know and you luck both days or.
Have it typed up and cited
this report of Fritz will be
a nice little type of for this by his check
up shows cause from tolerances phoned
the WM to spray with them and I suck at
them going the other way including one on
the seventh and several on the
eight the eight if you forgot is
a did and what will you accidental death
that oughta be enough to get an indictment
on the grand jury go pick it up
I'd like to play a long shot first it might
give us two for one well taken one at
a time
a bird in the hand is not going to lead
us to its mate. I'd like to give the lady
a little rope Well thanks
I thought you'd agree.
By the cannon that he just caught me out
again I have some rather startling news I
thought you should know before
it hits the head like. Me.
Down on the stand like that I asked him
about you it seems that your first hunch
remember that it take it was responsible
for your husband's death when Mrs Williams
You may have been right. I don't understand
your husband's briefcase turned up in
Kansas City yesterday in
a moving van that it stopped at the scene
of the accident that night apparently the
murderer made his getaway in it that
explains the wavy skid marks that made
a suspect your husband was ill or unconscious
at the time with the crash yes. I
suppose it does and by now the man is
probably asked the country and never will be
found to worry was William said they were
fingerprints on that briefcase and as
soon as we get the F.B.I.
Report from Washington is identity will be
known and he just trips and sent out on
police broadcast we'll find him all right
I just know we're keeping things quiet so
I'm overly feel safe until we are ready
to close in on him. Yes I can see the
wisdom of that. And thus you
would understand what it can.
As soon as we know his name it is possible
that you might recognize it is someone
with
a much there's that possibility you know
I'll do everything I can to help I'm
sure no way would I love you
given the I don't especially as
a robot and don't let it with
a. Bang
you're.
A We're.
A war with.
The poor. And one.
Dollar thirty five
C. Everything after the letter J.
In the first name has been obliterated by
heavy writing over it the only Empress
letters legible are those between words
for the four of them like are and have to
be under this name here and the hotel
Saturday or before the word Evanston.
Well Tom don't you think it's about time
you're retired why there isn't even
evidence there Mr Williams' intent to
communicate with Titans and who do you think
she beat
a path to the telegraph office to way into
the league of decency I'll tell you what
I think that should run around when I
first told you to the time you got
a notion to figure out
a way to pounce off you that much tougher
to find not unless she's tipped him off
from the office and he's got
it on ice waiting for you.
Getting better at writing
it all out I don't.
Have
a hard time you trying to
wreck that engine. Humor
it's
a hobby of mine. A way of going at it you
can't miss.
It I just can't let you ruin
a beautiful motor that direct. OK
starter up.
You through the night a mechanic
by trade and like that maybe it's
a hobby of mine.
He put out of your head
perhaps I was talking when I should
have been listening OK OK Then the
ha. Ha. Ha right now.
Give it away I get back I'm the book
I guess the new cars are a
little bit over my head now with
a jalopy is different either any mechanics
around or you can hire. A new factory
and then. I guess you got
better ways to. Break. How much
value to get it. And I'll
be shelling the police have
a Coke in the house you might as well.
Watch Can I use your phone and sister have
to go home today the other way but of
course. I hope for your. Flat tires this
morning no the dangler engine stalled on
my toes were so dry No I did not give you
the wrong number by saying you might want
to keep me out of repair beyond that to
a shame they gave me the wrong number
six five zero. And I still march
a few days in the modifying moment and
I'll be by my guest in a while he might do
a never want to talk about my
car again. Specially always.
OK. We're not so busy would you like
to do another good deed and give a man
a hand why not are a good karma
to maybe I can help get you
a good mechanic very good and very reasonable
for just what you need go but Iris.
Then I did the war Thanks for the
coke. I got on the been
fixed up all right nothing but
a sticky carburetor about by I'll
be paid you went for it only took
a minute you're certainly not
money conscious stranger. There.
Is not going to work for
a girl somebody's got to do it if I
want to stay in business and I want to.
Let the some business to do it better
suited for. A new lease this place to
somebody sure I did while my husband was
overseas but when he was killed in Okinawa
Well we made a lot of plans
for the future here and I had
a hunch he'd look at if I
took over and tried to make
a go the next morning I wanted to do that
I got along famously business has been
fine till lately when the help
got joy could be again I had
a good mechanic Yeah you sure need one
all right well for Pete's sake say
yes or no. He wants
a job you don't mean you to hire me
without knowing anything about me you can
repair automobiles what else do I
need to know that's your name well
I'm not sure I'll try it for
a while but you get someone permanents
the name Bill Walker OK feel it's
a deal and maybe it doesn't because you
know that you want to stay. I don't count
on this go on the rack.
It happens at some point
to have our shoulders like
a prize fighter. So I can pop up. For
everything going to go down the storytelling
. Oh gee
thanks. I'm sorry I would
have enough for the
day. Yet then.
Maybe you can use
a thousand from the slightly delirious
new. Thanks thing we haven't settled the
matter of wages yet maybe I can't tell you
regular salary I suppose we leave that
open to find out how much I'm worth to
the business it doesn't seem to be any
business right now might be a good time
for me to get out of this beer and find
a place to board we live right next door
Go Ask Mom to know the place or the
peaceful house I noticed that this morning
oh gosh I forgot she don't hoping this
will be with her canning mom find homes
for everything from stray cats to stray
mechanics. You're not
a stray anymore I'll go. For
a six. Dollars well from Africa mother
Hi Mom I've got some good news for you
all right and then for the station Yeah.
I know nobody we know he's from
he's not a town needs
a place aboard to go to sleep. OK
since you have to make
your first to go. And you
like Apple or cherry pie chart
Terry it is much. Too late and.
I gotta get rid of that. We're going to
earth barbershop the one and only just up
two blocks don't tell you working for me
when you get back we'll close up and go
home.
We'll. Look at the bringing up young
man thank you for the young man
the bank feels more for that
I found. A blessing. And
a new friend. I hope you're
putting hungry Mr Walker.
Who wouldn't think Marsh your sheep like
a sparrow with all the hard work she just
can't. Take but she can start taking it
in the box for help she never
takes anything as to put
a hold of our soul into everything she
does to the knowledge that you're with me
Bob how Bob Still it is sort of
a place where in this day we're
back anything right here we have
a spare bedroom going to wait. I
think you like my cooking like.
A very kind of you Mrs King but. It seems
in the position to position nothing
that's good business I know that
but I pay you one board room
a large one I think. If you'd like to say
we'd like to have you have more than.
Again you have a boarder. I have
a pretty good thing to do to make. Old
.
It's wonderful the way to come alive
in your hands you think sort of come
alive to have got real pleasure
out of working with I do
when you're doing
a job with them you can't think
of anything else you know if
something's bothering you why don't you
get rid of it. What would you prescribe
doctor. Amputation for the
stupid chip on your shoulder.
To.
Be desiring. The money. For
the baby and everything and
I just got
a flat out. That. I was
this credit good enough
for. Well. As collateral not
a chance fella never mind or I'll do it
on my own time thanks fail to see that I
had. Something you know
nothing you. Don't bother
nothing. But I. Was.
Right. There was
a con about there being hard up now. And
pretty tough one ever since you've. Fixed
a car for him to charge you for the labor
OK when you get to the free I don't rate
I'm not the man I say we could make an
anniversary present and over ten years
arrival mine three months
ago today. That was
a lucky day when you came to.
Your work then bringing in
a lot of business. For man on my meal.
They look wise why don't we three
celebrate the night and go to the movies
it's at the end date with. Let's mom out
to be babysitting I love to go Bill I haven't
been in ages if you're ever going to
. Work.
I need my arms however I have to read all
that extra time this is Sheila Graham
with the latest news of the shocking
Williams murder case while beautiful I mean
Williams held the trial charged with
conspiring to kill her late husband the police
are searching for James tons believed to
be the lover of Mrs Williams and have
a partner in the horrible
Madoff while telling him.
The fireman handling your case my dear Mrs
Williams I want one third of everything
you get. Out of Your Mind you don't
realize what I get is while it's without
perhaps you don't realize the spot you're
in charge his fingerprints were found not
only on your own briefcase but in
a manner of speaking on your reputation
as well there's an attack to the name
Quincy
a very smart cookie isn't exactly for you
frankly Miss to want and I'm beginning to
wonder if my attorneys on
underestimating their enemies
ammunition but scarce maybe why. If
we can get to trial before tarnishes
fall they'll never going
to conviction but. What
if he shows up we may have
to try him oh no that's not
cross that bridge until we
have to but if it comes to
a choice we're not going to burn are.
Not about that what about the fact you
know the rules are very broad because it
will gather you know those who do that in
the spring. Is there anything you don't
know. What Sam's just got that we have.
Better newspapers one thing anyway
California supposed to be the land of
opportunity. I thought of I know you
like that yes. I do. Very much.
Good. By people well boy. We
like it you. Know only Oh you'd be surprised
how many people ask questions about
you. What kind of question old
boy you came from to have
any family do you like it here and are
you going to stay. El noticed me at the
movie last night he wanted to join
a volunteer fire department just interested
friendly things. I suppose it is
natural for people to wonder about
a stranger move into their community
like I did. You know I've been thinking.
Maybe but that's
a good idea you're not going to the movies
last night it's all right being seen in
the station here with Mom but. You get
used to town as you're always trying to.
Marry people. Just ignore it and after
a while and forgettable. I'll
go get cleaned up for so.
Long in. Order.
You know it tell you how many years the
Sunday fix get back did you always fall
asleep during the sermon or in the sleep
with Peter. I merely closed my eyes to
concentrate off no matter
what. I did not know I mean.
Why is. It disturbing I
reckon that. It is well.
To be the same be present in the brain or.
As they say you can pick up boy out of
the country but polling still get lost.
And has stopped rolling
sometimes doesn't. And.
We go very becoming shade of moss
here in our. Country today. To go
a lot and I think. Anyone
in particular. And
that's good to hear that. Someone
cord out of the book. You
married on to do. The right.
Must have loved her very much to have been
hurt so deeply. She saw afraid someone
even yourself. Maybe it's
better that way. And no one
gets hurt. Bitterness and hatred hurt
everyone. Can see that they don't.
Feel like
a wall that chucked out all the sunshine
from the garden and that everything where
they. Make room in your heart
for something else can you.
Guess this is my day for sermon.
So I. As Mama say you never
get rich my dear the
filesystem. Alright the paper
to borrow
a curiosity
a Erakat
a ward
a big day Amaro
a
way
of Iraq and
poor guy a a P.S.A.
a Gag
a war
rag
tag Nowadays I'm here to help Mrs
Wesley find a couple of guys
a picture so you help the
can of thank you. But I
deliver the Dakar insists that I have
a fight with him for the bought of
a backlash very funny stuff. What
a day. It would be ideal
for you donning my socks.
Well I thought I'd go up the Holy One
doesn't doing you much good. I found I want
to look fresh papers in your
view are you. Sure you have
a heap of things that need mending having
just. Done Marcia No Do you think I'd
tell her this is
a problem. Because I found out about it
doesn't give me the right to tell anyone
else not even Marcia. When you trust broken
trust and giving him the chance to work
out I mean the way that he
brightened them. Up and one of
them women will. Don't brigantine
a lot easier to be tolerant and understanding
of that. Then and guess at what do
you. Mean young on line number
my grandma found me on.
The in.
The. Family home.
There are you in there. Yeah Mom went
next door Hi you were gone leaning Obama
for. Anything more. And I
want to tell you something
I'm checking out for something happen
you know I'm doing what I should
have done
a long time ago moving along
but why Bill my name isn't
even Bill written on it Bill Walker I'm
Walter Williams the late for William
Ward Williams. I don't understand you
may not even after I told you but at
least you know the whole story so that we.
Finally Larkspur. And you.
From there on you know.
I'm glad you're going back to make things
right going back wild horses couldn't
drag me back. What are you going to do
about your wife nothing's going to go to
trial for murder oh no bill why not she
tried to kill me she and her cousin but
they didn't who said they didn't but then
try and prove that. No matter what why
did you get be tried for something
it didn't happen will be
a Can't you see but I can see she deserves
everything she's getting very part of it
as they'll never convict her nobody and
the SO I part is you're not big enough to
take
a hard job to your pride and your ego. It
hurts to be tricked into device someone
you love and believe in but that doesn't
give you the right to take justice into
your own hands and to trample on the
heart of others and walk out on my.
Barren frustrated boy. A marriage to
a woman or accepted my love. Despite your
sort of federally she resorted to murder
. I never think about names
together without remorse. For their
degraded. In getting me the more.
Please. Don't destroy the one chance. We
haven't got
a chance. Doing the right thing never
works out I know and that's where
a good turn the other cheek NIF with
a lot of French. Born. Brian forgive me.
More.
Right. Now that I'm here to undertake
a. New. Thing each and every.
Year. For it.
Not to get the big
a hard job you're pioneering. It hurt to
be checked into it if I thought you love
me. But that doesn't give you the right to
take justice into your own hands travel
on the heart of others
and. Don't just want
to.
Ah. Poor boy.
Who has.
Mrs Peters was kind enough to come
along to substantiate at least
a large proportion of what I call it very
thoughtful of him as he does Mr Williams
When you read in the newspaper that the
hitchhiker who attacked you had been
a close friend of the always for
some time it must have been
a great shock to you I didn't come here to
discuss my emotional reactions with that
and if you need me for anything further
got from my office window or to reach me
let's go Mike just
a minute Mr Williams We need your signed
statement for the grand jury when we ask
for your wife's release it
won't take long to type.
Them in.
This is with humans have
news. Really I can get
a way. Who
has.
Put. James It was Thomas who
was in the common and I.
Don't know the Mel
did you kill him you know
he tried to kill me but he had
and he ran into the truck
it was an accident. Next you
wait only to tell this story
you might be wrong in this
filthy jail weight of
a scale that everybody believe you're dead.
Pretty convenient spot and I'm dead man
can't be tried on that issue in your
production wife would understand better if you
would explain to her about the amnesia
to me. Don't tell me you believe he had
anything when he put it all this time just
wandering around to take. Care of this
he's been in Larkspur little
town and I don't working as
a mechanic in the service station
run by this is Peter's Yeah
I understand now that my
chance for happiness is dead
I suppose you demand
a divorce I thank you to give me so that
I could marry him that's fantastic yes
changing that after you telling
us that the man you picked up was
a pushy strange and that's not true of
the time and place of meeting him at all
been a right I must advise you there's
a lot of the life can't testify
against us but there's
a law against murder too but that didn't
stop him and nothing's going to stop me
until I'm through all
right with me Captain
go on talk your head off
I was to have gone with him to dance and
he insisted on it although I was quite
pale seven hours before all of the
to leave and he came home there was
a pilot to see and he threatened to kill
me unless I agreed to give up him. And I
wish he had this incredible.
Not one word that she has said is true but
when your mother knew more about this
man or was there
a witness to the threats you mentioned
no I must for made overhead
she was in the apartment in fact she picked
up the pieces of the bank that he threw
at me first you know. I don't know she she
left me Saturday after all this began.
Because the questions wait up I feel that.
You have this is when you're trying to
be the grand jury ten o'clock
tomorrow morning that's all
we're going to hold you to Williams
On what charge suspicion of murder
but he's not guilty of any of these things
but it should be easy for him to prove
it taken down because that fiction of Mrs
Williams must have been very convincing
you know we just couldn't buy that
Janya trying to set it to go. Like
a reality check on her you know. That is
a way to walk to rewind
a very fine thank you like me well
when you're married whining about your
I mean when you. Get
a fresh. Water like a car or
a wife and really is going to couple
Williams off OK boys hop to it I want all I
can get by telling them are the grand
jury will get you oh Tom Don't miss
a bit of everything you can on billions
on the Peter Dame you sort of believe I
read William story didn't you and she
made better sense and it will show she's
a better life than he is going to get I
went all through the grieving we do it with
she's
a bad customer where Let's for the grand
jury decide Williams insisted on having
a talk so it is funeral funeral right there
specially with that you know need to
look my dish out of character for him. If
you pieces missing somewhere I might be
and I don't know if it's not too much out
of character for you to get going you're
going to miss me when I retired next year
maybe I'll join private eye and Savill
cases for. Mr Williams
Back to deal from the bottom here
going to start with you OK with him.
Well I've very good news judging from
your faces while the grand jury returns
indictment against you Mrs
Williams was released
a thief and I don't show where I walk away
I have your back at work where you are
needed and Shar come on average there's
a visitor waiting far more attractive than
we all hope. For just leaving Mrs Peters
But remember don't hesitate to call
me for anything thank you so much.
I'd love. To know what have I done to
you if it weren't for me you wouldn't
be here if it weren't for you I
wouldn't be I came back here because
I wanted to believe in the things you do
I still do no matter what happened. We
didn't want to. Go back home
right away or be taken care of.
Not it seems you like to think of a
better reason than that to get ready. I'm
a big one now. And you've
just been left for Williams
when they found these newspaper to be the
course some of them were three months old
but you seem to treasure them so I brought
him along so I don't take the exactly
substantiate your claim of amnesia. As if
you are interested in substantiating any
claim of mine now let's get one thing
straight most people when they get in
a jam think the police are only interested
in the prosecution I would job is to get
the facts the truth and the truth never
hurt anyone but the feeling that like I
left you with a beautiful woman a
quick kidney Williams You meet
a Buddha I have no more to do with Taurus
death but you will get out of the whole
population of Northern California you
just happen to pick up on the child who
happened to be your wife's boyfriend. We're
going to. Show the truth when you take
the stand but you better have some monkey
conclusive proof if you expect the jury
to believe it way the tenant will we all
know you're not guilty but we're going to
need help to prove it and need it badly so
technically he can't take sides that are
part of right he has to
be on ours and I have
a hunch he wants to but he went
into telling the whole story all of
it so yes I'd like to thank
you very much I guess I should have
told the whole truth in the first
place but I want to clean this mess
up with as little scandal as possible
where no sign of the lug wrench or anything
made the images viewed as we'll please
stop trying to be
a good take how many times do you think
the police of course in this spot put any
kind of evidence now be
a nice spin take Mr Williams advice go back
to Luxor What time is it it's only four
o'clock we still have time to go back down
and go out to hunt pursue land Now look
here young woman you have had me on the
run since early Monday but Lieutenant the
maid seems to be our only hope now we've
got to keep looking do we find that so I
told when she was naturalized wasn't
she suffering sharp sticks Quincey you
don't fly for this shit is sure
what's your name was Chinese born if
a port of entry wish I would
just go that still be
a high on earth Porto and all
of this go. Back to town
immigration.
Well the council has given
us the right leave.
You watching. Understand.
Usually English also
French Italian and Hebrew. Name
one asked what is desired really
pursuing SHAWN But Jenny Jones you said
you were uncle and why does what she is
this daughter of my brother she's
a friend of the honorable police Oh no I
just want to ask her some questions about
Mr Williams And then she used to work for.
Asking so hard is he that he cannot lead
you to her but things that are not and
cannot be told where you're emitting over
the border to heck with.
Him. Untruths is not good for soul and not
wisdom when told police were better for
the soul to be kind and to be why we must
keep silence to help in this matter.
You know you're quite again in case they
haven't totally. You just to ease the
theme. There must be
a way out why can't we
find. Tomorrow today.
Yesterday you're going to try.
And the state intends to provide any
reasonable doubt that the president walked
away the others did it with malice
aforethought kill the deceased chambers times
only knew how to be's wife's lover and
then with these victim dead beside him he
drove his car into the course of an
oncoming truck jumping clear yourself some
seconds prior to the crash and subsequently
made his getaway in the back of an old
photo band and for three months
says Bill Walker he left
a justice but it imprisoned his unfaithful
wife conspiracy in his own murder but
then decided that being dead cramped his
style he thought he could ease cake and
have it too so he returned most anxious
to explain his long absence and to write
the dreadful mistake that imprisoned his
wife for three months maybe some gentlemen
it was
a cold blooded premeditated murder must
be punished to the fullest extent of the
long haul the first witness please Captain
Callahan did want to Williams tell you
what suddenly cured his amnesia after three
months no he did not but he did tell
you demanded struck the blow which
caused the amnesia was a total stranger
a hitchhiker it picked up yes and that he
knew nothing of this man's identity your
relationship with his wife until he suddenly
recovered from his amnesia and heard
or read the details of what he said Oh
thank you have to. Witness the House voted
no question for a moment no
I saw no signs of amnesia
a definite concussion because if it was
based IF an option question but not very
eager unsure in your opinion Dr could
this head injury have been caused by
a fall as if they had it struck on
some object such as a stone home nor
a metal pipe at all thank you it would
not have any there are you familiar with
a tool known as the lug wrench for changing
automobile wheels I'm afraid I am sure
I've had
a regular epidemic of flat tires lately
well then in your opinion could this head
injury which you treated have
been caused by a blow from
a large wrench Yes. It could have been
caused by that too thank you doctor the ones
with the earliest are heavily creased as
though they've been carrying a wallet or
a coat pocket Thank you. Would you kindly
tell the court where you found these
newspaper clippings.
Is this your handwriting.
And that's the message.
Would you read it to the court please.
Mr Williams call said he
want you to forget all about
a problem that is going to take
their only was there any other
conversation well I just asked if
that was all and he said yes she'll
understand. And for the laughter. So joke.
Around the prosecution and it was like
grim faced with return the. Girl will
be after he takes the stand is
anybody's guess but he's going. To get
a decision and don't torrent struck with
intent to kill after telling you this is
from Iran and the second you're still
telephoned Illinois to find out if there was
a cousin Jim. You are hard to convince
aren't you Mr What is it so incredible that
a man should fight against believing such
a thing about his wife all that is very
touching from a husband who planned
a trip on which he intended to destroy
his wife and did kill her lover that's
a lie. I object to the conclusion drawn
by the prosecutor and the second to the
right but your honor there is
a cover so let's remember was
your wife's lover. There's
also her own story which in front of
witnesses you insisted she town and then we
have your own two different stories
from your own lips one featuring
a perfectly strange hitchhiker. Second an
equally strange cousin Jim said on the
question of the vantage
point of. The new day.
With.
The pilot.
And.
The rules.
For the. Week.
Where. The swear the the.
Movie with you Soledad.
So Daniel you're saying you were never me
don't you I was here we're going to quit
even the police department I just ball is
going up the stairs I start coming here.
You must be mistaken I'm not mistaken
she's here I must hear I think don't you
understand it to save
a man from prison even from death. Like
. She was doing good on all of. Us to
live and we've been looking for you
all these weeks Mr Williams need your help
so desperately I cannot help you must
forget the two found soon and forget it but
you're the only witness you're the only
mother going to help not as
a witness only with silence can I repay
his great kindness to me and my family in
China why I heard of the things that most
unhappy day for Mrs Williams bedrooms
boys Fiddy loud and angry parties broken
to pieces he can explain all the hell they
do not believe what he has already told
that I heard anything would do harm don't
seem
much sorrow comes from women who know not
honor and truth and Mrs Williams she was
not true even to that Torrance man what
makes you say that that night when he was
killed her sickness was booked wall up for
good beyond which she could go secretly
to
a meeting place. You mean
she went out that night Sue
Lynn are you sure yes because next morning
in her bedroom I found street shoes that
had been warm or cold on the closet floor
with the sleeves turned inside out as
though removed hurriedly and in one pocket
a door key to some hotel to lend that's it
proved that she and tore it had planned
to meet that night after he killed
Mr Williams what hotel was it on
I don't remember the key. What did
you do with it return to cold pocket
Come on we'll get to dinner Quincy he'll
know what to do and prays to mine every
step of the way.
I hold everything even if this long shot
don't wake up we just keep on Pigeon.
Oh I love you even. More.
I think one hundred eighty here is yes.
Room three hundred two airport hotel. Maybe
we got our miracle especially the Chinese
one bit in the hope that small help to
thing we have always. Picked up open
precious little hotel run people.
Always are nice to have an all right but
I sure don't remember looking like this
quite a dish a little too he sees a
united us and thinks that I just found
a couple of cars for the three zero
two one July. Thanks to move Mr and
Mrs Jaybird room not slip to.
Look couldn't see the handwriting on the
card identical to that in the photograph
is a little boy the same thing
because. I look at impressions J.
Here and here R.N.'s J.
That's the name she started
a telegram to room that's left him saying
I got that Van Praag novel town she said
to be out of the room by midnight
is one of them was catching
a plane. Whoever
made this time in history this ties it all
up does need the leg agrees pig What do
you mean we've got the evidence now the
proof of what sealed it is theory that I
mean which claim the view this evidence
only proves that you gave me to keep what
did with
a man named Burns we can't even prove that
he didn't keep the deed but you know he
didn't there wasn't anybody it was only
a name that Seon towards you claim if you
can prove that Williams will be freed but
none of this you prove it sorry copper but
we are just another blind alley right
S.E. Cupp a sample case from
a sad man about myspace this
morning I'll be right away.
To.
See it. Because of this force of
water where you proceed Mr Allred
your honor we will call
Mrs Irene will you. Take
a stab Mrs Williams
raise your right hand and you saw me so I
think that the money by giving this got
to be the truth the whole truth and nothing
but the two South I don't want cooks
the things fall into Mr Howard what's the
purpose in calling this witness merely
for preppers of identifying
handwriting. Now Mrs Williams This
photograph of you was stolen from my
apartment so according to the description to
walk my adoring of the door of husband
Irene this belongs to Mr Williams This is
your handwriting is new cos I'm touched
that they should have bought it so badly
and this telegram addressed to Mrs
Margaret clobbered with that also your
handwriting it has.
No Mrs Burns I mean Mrs Williams This
photograph is inscribed To Jim my
adoring and adored Irene did you write
this too I see no point at all this merely
answer counsel's questions did you write
that I did and these letters addressed to
Mr James Torrance that you write them yes
and this monogrammed garment of gift from
you to Mr Torrance fine if I be tortured
again by all this I never made any secret
of my love to Jim Tarrant That's why I
get your love for Jim times in the
very night he was killed you had
a rendezvous with
a man named bones than Joe I don't know
what you're talking about I don't know any
man named her and I was at home that type
area Oh yes they're sleeping pills Well
you must walk in your sleep there for us
but of these part of that night of the
airport hotel in Oakland where
you registered for Mr and Mrs J.
Bowman always the court's time trying to
deny it this is the registration card that
you signed at nine twenty pm and there is
a room clerical resigned you to roam free
all to and this Mrs Williams is the key
to room three hundred two which you
very carelessly left in the pocket of
a coat which was found in your closet
yesterday all right I was there how you said
it I had not quite. This J.
Burns Mrs Williams first name Jack yet
anyone can say with a going no no Holmes
a gypsy know very well as Jack but what
I don't know I don't remember that she
doesn't remember because there isn't any
Jack Burns and there never was that was an
alias for Jim Torrance and it was parents
who was to have met you that night after
your charming little plot to kill your
husband at the duty executed after oh it's
not true I have bad news for you Mrs
Williams I can prove it's true these pajamas
these letters this picture all of which
you identified by the court were found in
this suitcase. Which is full of the close
and personal belongings of Mr James
tolerance and the suitcase was found in the
baggage room of the airport hotel where
he's been held since June ninth and
it says on his tag in large print
hold for Jack Byrne That
is almost what it was
just
a moment Mrs Williams Your Honor in view
of the evidence presented and we now ask
for
a dismissal of the state's case against
Walter Williams and we intend to charge Irene
Williams with conspiracy to commit murder
against her husband Walter Williams. On
the ice.
Age against water gleams dismissed
art adjourned until two o'clock.
And I swear that that was graduation
was with him. Actually. I haven't
a word for it thank you but we we can never
made it without you know how to use it
with you know son like
always with me if you with
a little push especially when you get
a couple like this when you do the put you
know when I be seeing you you know to
simply to scream to be able to eat and sleep
without someone get in the air all the
time. Oh firewalled we're looking forward
to having on and on the way we get to
Denver pleasure waiting for your op on
the second leg of the morning. About
a conflict you bet you can't I'll do
it well I'll be running off. You think
you'll like them but. It's
OK by me boss. Catch. Him.
Force with which to lies can come together
sometimes for evil sometimes for good.
With
a reality. He. Has
with whom.
We ate
a feeling
with one where.